Can you keep a national secret?
Kill the Messenger is a crime, drama, mystery film directed by Michael Cuesta.
A reporter becomes the target of a vicious smear campaign that drives him to the point of suicide after he
exposes the CIA's role in arming Contra rebels in Nicaragua and importing cocaine into California.
Based on the true story of journalist Gary Webb.
Gary Webb, played by Jeremy Renner.
Anna Simons, played by Mary Elizabeth Winstead.
Fred Weil, played by Michael Sheen.
John Cullen, played by Ray Liotta.
Ronny Quail, played by Robert Patrick.
Norwin Meneses, played by Andy Garcia.
Kill the Messenger is a 2014 American biographical crime thriller film
directed by Michael Cuesta and written by Peter Landesman.
It is based on the book of the same name by Nick Schou
and the book Dark Alliance by Gary Webb.
The film stars Jeremy Renner, who also produced the film.
The film was released on October 10, 2014, and depicts a reporter's suppressed attempts to cover the CIA
involvement and secret support of large scale cocaine sales to fund the Nicaraguan Contras.
The film explores themes of central intelligence agency (cia), drug
trafficking, biography, crack cocaine, government conspiracy.
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.